HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005: A Finding Aid
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005
- Series I. Faculty Photographs, 1908-2005
  - Subseries A. Faculty Photographs, A-Z, 1908-2005
    - E. Robert Livernash- Receiving an Honorary Decoration from His Imperial Majesty Shahanshah Aryamehr, presented by HIH Prince Abdorezza., 1975 (Box 17)
    - Charles Atkins Livesey, circa 1945 (Box 17)
    - Sharon Marecki Livesey, circa 1988 (Box 17)
    - Sharon Marecki Livesey, 1989 (Box 17)
    - J. Sterling Livingston, 1948-1969 (Box 17)
    - J. Sterling Livingston- Teaching, circa 1970 (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, circa 1965 (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, 1965 (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, 1970 (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, 1973 (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, 1984 (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, 1989 (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, 1990s (Box 17)
    - George Cabot Lodge, circa 2000 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard- Teaching, 1946 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard, 1947 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard- At General Motors Conference, 1947 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard, circa 1950 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard- With Harriet O. Ronken, Paul R. Lawrence, and Abraham Zaleznik, circa 1950 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard, circa 1962 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard, 1966 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard, 1978 (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard, 1980s (Box 17)
    - George F.F. Lombard- At Organizational Behavior Conference, 1982 (Box 17)
    - George F. F. Lombard, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - George F. F. Lombard, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Harold S. Lord, circa 1950 (Box 17)
    - Jay W. Lorsch- With Paul R. Lawrence, circa 1965 (Box 17)
    - Jay W. Lorsch, 1969 (Box 17)
    - Jay W. Lorsch, 1970 (Box 17)
    - Jay W. Lorsch, 1977 (Box 17)
    - Jay W. Lorsch, circa 1980 (Box 17)
    - Jay W. Lorsch- With John Gabarro and Gary Loveman, 1990 (Box 17)
    - Michael L. Lovdal, circa 1980 (Box 17)
    - Osgood S. Lovekin, 1932 (Box 17)
    - Christopher H. Lovelock, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Christopher H. Lovelock, circa 1980 (Box 17)
    - Gary W. Loveman, circa 1989 (Box 17)
    - A. Lawrence Lowell, circa 1920 (Box 17)
    - Timothy A. Luehrman, circa 1990 (Box 17)
    - Robert T. Lund, circa 1971 (Box 17)
    - Arromanus Coleman Lyles, circa 1967 (Box 17)
    - Harry H. Lynch, circa 1968 (Box 17)
    - Myles Mace, 1938-1948 (Box 18)
    - Myles Mace, 1952 (Box 18)
    - Myles Mace, circa 1955 (Box 18)
    - Myles Mace- Obtaining a case, circa 1955, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Myles Mace- Presenting First National Bank of Cleveland, Ohio Fellowship Awards, 1964-1965 (Box 18)
    - Myles Mace, circa 1970 (Box 18)
    - John J. Madigan, 1930 (Box 18)
    - Modesto A. Maidique, circa 1980 (Box 18)
    - David H. Maister, 1979 (Box 18)
    - David H. Maister, 1982 (Box 18)
    - Claudine Malone, 1972 (Box 18)
    - Claudine Malone- Teaching, circa 1972 (Box 18)
    - Claudine Malone, circa 1979 (Box 18)
    - Claudine Malone- Teaching, 1979 (Box 18)
    - Thomas W. Malone, circa 1993 (Box 18)
    - Deane Waldo Malott, 1935 (Box 18)
    - Deane Waldo Malott, circa 1950, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Robert H. Malott, circa 1953 (Box 18)
    - Dr. James S. Mansfield, 1950s (Box 18)
    - Charles C. Manz, circa 1988 (Box 18)
    - Jesse W. Markham, 1968-circa 1970 (Box 18)
    - Jesse W. Markham, 1980s (Box 18)
    - Constatinos C. Markides, circa 1985 (Box 18)
    - Wesley W. Marple, circa 1957 (Box 18)
    - Gordon L. Marshall, circa 1963 (Box 18)
    - Martin V. Marshall, 1956 (Box 18)
    - Martin V. Marshall, 1960s (Box 18)
    - Martin V. Marshall, circa 1980 (Box 18)
    - Paul W. Marshall, circa 1968-circa 1975 (Box 18)
    - Albro Martin, 1976 (Box 18)
    - Albro Martin, 1980s (Box 18)
    - Boyce Ficklen Martin, 1935-1940 (Box 18)
    - John Henry Martin, 1939 (Box 18)
    - Selden O. Martin, circa 1912 (Box 18)
    - Scott P. Mason, 1979 (Box 18)
    - Scott P. Mason, 1980s (Box 18)
    - Scott P. Mason, 1983 (Box 18)
    - Robert Louis Masson, 1932-1948 (Box 18)
    - Robert Louis Masson, 1960s (Box 18)
    - Robert Louis Masson, 1961 (Box 18)
    - Robert Louis Masson, circa 1965 (Box 18)
    - Robert Louis Masson, 1970 (Box 18)
    - John B. Matthews, 1950s (Box 18)
    - John B. Matthews, 1978-1987 (Box 18)
    - John J. Mauriel, Jr., circa 1965 (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo- Clippings related to photographs (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo, circa 1927 (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo, circa 1935 (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo- With Fritz J. Roethlisberger, circa 1940 (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo- Looking at charts, Photograph by Joseph Breitenbach, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo- Looking at charts, Photograph by Joseph Breitenbach, 1946, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Elton Mayo, circa 1947 (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo, 1947 (Box 18)
    - Elton Mayo and George F. F. Lombard at Weekend Conference on Human Relations, 10-11 May 1947, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - John H. McArthur, 1959-1968 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, 1968 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, 1970 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, 1979 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur- HBS Christmas party, circa 1980 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, 1980s (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, 1980 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur- At alumni event, 1983 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, 1984 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, circa 1985 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - John H. McArthur, 1986 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur- At alumni event, 1986 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, 1989 (Box 18)
    - John H. McArthur, circa 1995 (Box 18)
    - Thomas B. McCabe, circa 1973 (Box 18)
    - Michael B. McCaskey, circa 1973 (Box 18)
    - Michael B. McCaskey, 1982 (Box 18)
    - Hassell H. McClellan, circa 1976 (Box 19)
    - Janice McCormick, 1980s (Box 19)
    - Andrew M. McCosh, circa 1950 (Box 19)
    - Thomas McCraw, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Thomas McCraw- Teaching, 1980s (Box 19)
    - Thomas McCraw, 1990s (Box 19)
    - Thomas McCraw- Portraits, 1995 (Box 19)
    - Alphonse McDonald, circa 1990 (Box 19)
    - John G. McDonald, 1986 (Box 19)
    - F. Warren McFarlan, circa 1965 (Box 19)
    - F. Warren McFarlan, 1970s (Box 19)
    - F. Warren McFarlan, circa 1980 (Box 19)
    - F. Warren McFarlan, 1980s (Box 19)
    - F. Warren McFarlan- With Jim McKenney and Guy Parson, circa 1990 (Box 19)
    - Ross Armstrong McFarland, circa 1939 (Box 19)
    - Anita McGahan, circa 1995 (Box 19)
    - Robert E. McGarrah, circa 1960 (Box 19)
    - Kenneth Chaffee McIntosh, 1943 (Box 19)
    - Kenneth Chaffee McIntosh, 1947 (Box 19)
    - Michael J. McIntyre, circa 1980 (Box 19)
    - James L. McKenney, circa 1960-1965 (Box 19)
    - Ed McKinley, circa 1950 (Box 19)
    - Curtis P. McLaughlin, circa 1960 (Box 19)
    - John Godfrey McLean, circa 1942 (Box 19)
    - John Godfrey McLean- Teaching, 1943 (Box 19)
    - John Godfrey McLean, circa 1950 (Box 19)
    - John Godfrey McLean- Teaching, 1952 (Box 19)
    - William Henry McLean, 1935-1948 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Clippings related to photographs (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1920s (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1930s (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1940s (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, circa 1940 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1949 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- On cover of Business Week magazine, 29 January 1949 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1950s (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Filene Professorship Dinner, 1950 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Retail Merchants' Council, 6 February 1952 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, January 1954 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Party for Donald K. David, circa 1955 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Obtaining a case, circa 1955, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- With John Lintner and Neil Borden, circa 1955 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, circa 1960 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, circa 1960, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- Headshots by Fabian Bachrach, circa 1960 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1961 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- On cover of Retail Control magazine, November 1964 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, December 1964 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, 1965 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair- On cover of Department Store Economist magazine, Apri; 1966 (Box 19)
    - Malcolm P. McNair, circa 1970 (Box 19)
    - Robert Strange McNamara, 1939 (Box 19)
    - Russell Blair McNeill, circa 1946 (Box 19)
    - Russell Blair McNeill- With Edward B. McKinley, 1949 (Box 19)
    - John Peter McNerney, circa 1956 (Box 19)
    - Melissa Mead, circa 1986 (Box 19)
    - Dudley H. Meek, circa 1956 (Box 19)
    - Kenneth A. Merchant, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Richard Stockton Meriam, circa 1930-1938 (Box 19)
    - Richard Stockton Meriam, 1944-1946 (Box 19)
    - Richard Stockton Meriam- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 19)
    - Richard Stockton Meriam- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Richard Stockton Meriam, 1956 (Box 19)
    - Richard Stockton Meriam, 1960s (Box 19)
    - Robert W. Merry, 1939-1948 (Box 20)
    - Robert W. Merry, 1949 (Box 20)
    - Robert W. Merry, 1951 (Box 20)
    - Robert W. Merry, 1960- circa 1965 (Box 20)
    - Robert W. Merry, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
    - Robert W. Merry, circa 1970 (Box 20)
    - Gale Merseth, circa 1980 (Box 20)
    - Jean-Francois Mertens, circa 1990 (Box 20)
    - Robert C. Merton, circa 1988 (Box 20)
    - Robert C. Merton, circa 1993 (Box 20)
    - Robert C. Merton, 1995 (Box 20)
    - Robert C. Merton, 1997 (Box 20)
    - Robert C. Merton, 2002 (Box 20)
    - Emmanuel Mesthene, circa 1965 (Box 20)
    - John R. Meyer, circa 1980 (Box 20)
    - Richard F. Meyer, circa 1965 (Box 20)
    - Richard F. Meyer, circa 2000 (Box 20)
    - Robert H. Miles, 1980s (Box 20)
    - Robert H. Miles, circa 1980 (Box 20)
    - Robert H. Miles- With Arvind Bhambri, 1984 (Box 20)
    - Robert H. Miles, circa 1985 (Box 20)
    - Robert H. Miles- Teaching, circa 1985 (Box 20)
    - Jeffrey G. Miller, circa 1974 (Box 20)
    - Raymond Miller- With C. Leigh Stevens and Donald K. David, circa 1955 (Box 20)
    - Raymond Miller- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 20)
    - Raymond Miller, 1956 (Box 20)
    - Raymond Miller, 1958 (Box 20)
    - Raymond Miller, 1959 (Box 20)
    - Raymond Miller, 1960s (Box 20)
    - Stanley Miller, 1950s (Box 20)
    - Stanley Miller, 1950 (Box 20)
    - Stanley Miller- With John McLean, circa 1953 (Box 20)
    - Stanley Miller, circa 1980 (Box 20)
    - Daniel Quinn Mills, circa 1990 (Box 20)
    - Robert J.T. Minichiello, circa 1965 (Box 20)
    - Kazuhiro Mishina, 1991 (Box 20)
    - David Moment, 1960s (Box 20)
    - Graham Eyres Monsell, 1937 (Box 20)
    - Cynthia A. Montgomery, circa 1989 (Box 20)
    - Ronald W. Moore, circa 1972- circa 1985 (Box 20)
    - John R. Moot, 1948 (Box 20)
    - Henry M. Morgan, circa 1974 (Box 20)
    - Roger A. More, circa 1975 (Box 20)
    - Eileen Morley, circa 1973- circa 1980 (Box 20)
    - Edwin L. Morris, 1935 (Box 20)
    - Edwin L. Morris, circa 1960 (Box 20)
    - James C. Morrison, circa 1988 (Box 20)
    - Alexander L. Mortin, circa 1965 (Box 20)
    - Jack Moscatelli, circa 1972 (Box 20)
    - Robert W. Mullins, circa 1976 (Box 20)
    - John M. Mulvey, circa 1976 (Box 20)
    - Dennis E. Mulvihill, circa 1970 (Box 20)
    - Donlin P. Murdy, 1934 (Box 20)
    - Kevin J. Murphy, 1990s (Box 20)
    - John E. Murray, circa 1965 (Box 20)
    - Clark E. Myers, circa 1955 (Box 20)
    - Laura Nash, 1980s (Box 20)
    - Laura Nash- With Ken Goodpaster, circa 1982 (Box 20)
    - Thomas R. Navin, 1948-circa 1950 (Box 20)
    - Judson Neff, 1942 (Box 20)
    - Judson Neff- Teaching, 1943 (Box 20)
    - Judson Neff- Teaching, circa 1944 (Box 20)
    - Judson Neff- Teaching, 1946 (Box 20)
    - Judson Neff- Teaching, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Eric Neilson, 1970s (Box 20)
    - Joseph William Newman- Teaching, circa 1953 (Box 21)
    - Joseph William Newman, circa 1957 (Box 21)
    - Derek A. Newton, circa 1955 (Box 21)
    - Abraham Jacob Neyman, 1980s (Box 21)
    - Clarence B. Nickerson, 1930-1948 (Box 21)
    - Clarence B. Nickerson, 1949 (Box 21)
    - Clarence B. Nickerson, circa 1950 (Box 21)
    - Clarence B. Nickerson- With student, circa 1965 (Box 21)
    - Clarence B. Nickerson, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Clarence B. Nickerson, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Powell Niland, 1948- circa 1955 (Box 21)
    - Nitin Nohria, circa 1990 (Box 21)
    - Richard L. Nolan, circa 1960-circa 1965 (Box 21)
    - Richard L. Nolan, circa 1975 (Box 21)
    - Richard L. Nolan, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Wilson Nolen, 1956-1961 (Box 21)
    - Patrick S. Noonan, circa 1993 (Box 21)
    - Nancy P. Norton, circa 1955 (Box 21)
    - Robert E.M. Nourse, circa 1967-circa 1975 (Box 21)
    - Christopher Edward Nugent, circa 1972 (Box 21)
    - David W. Nylen, circa 1960 (Box 21)
    - Warren Oksman, circa 1975 (Box 21)
    - Robert E. Olive, circa 1960 (Box 21)
    - Robert E. Olson, circa 1960 (Box 21)
    - Charles D. Orth, III, circa 1954 (Box 21)
    - Lynn Sharp Paine, circa 1991 (Box 21)
    - Krishna G. Palepu, circa 1984 (Box 21)
    - Steven R. Palesy, circa 1978 (Box 21)
    - James A. Parker, 1933 (Box 21)
    - James E. Parks, circa 1956 (Box 21)
    - Sharon D. Parks, 1990s (Box 21)
    - Gregory L. Parsons, circa 1980 (Box 21)
    - Calvin H.P. Pava, 1984 (Box 21)
    - Andrall E. Pearson, circa 1986 (Box 21)
    - Merton J. Peck, circa 1960 (Box 21)
    - Stanton Peele, circa 1980 (Box 21)
    - George S. Peer, circa 1955 (Box 21)
    - Andre F. Perold, circa 1980 (Box 21)
    - Andre F. Perold, 1991 (Box 21)
    - Robert L. Peterson, circa 1963 (Box 21)
    - Charles I. Petschek, 1948 (Box 21)
    - Jeffrey Pfeffer, circa 1982 (Box 21)
    - Lynn W. Phillips, circa 1985 (Box 21)
    - Howard W. Pifer, III, circa 1970 (Box 21)
    - Wilbert A. Pinkerton, Jr., circa 1970s (Box 21)
    - Thomas R. Piper, circa 1970 (Box 21)
    - Thomas R. Piper, circa 1975 (Box 21)
    - Thomas R. Piper, 1978- circa 1980 (Box 21)
    - Thomas R. Piper- Teaching, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Thomas R. Piper, circa 1990 (Box 21)
    - Gary P. Pisano, circa 1989 (Box 21)
    - Gary P. Pisano, circa 1990 (Box 21)
    - William J. Poorvu, circa 1974 (Box 21)
    - William J. Poorvu, circa 1980 (Box 21)
    - William J. Poorvu, circa 2000 (Box 21)
    - Dan Pope, circa 1980 (Box 21)
    - Kenneth W. Porter, 1935 (Box 21)
    - Michael E. Porter, circa 1975 (Box 21)
    - Michael E. Porter- With John Roland Fox, Michael Beer, and Joseph Auerbach, circa 1985 (Box 21)
    - Michael E. Porter, 1986 (Box 21)
    - Michael E. Porter, circa 1990 (Box 21)
    - Patrick Glenn Porter, circa 1971 (Box 21)
    - James T.S. Porterfield, circa 1956 (Box 21)
    - Reed Powell, circa 1960 (Box 21)
    - Joseph A. Pratt, circa 1983 (Box 21)
    - Lee E. Preston, circa 1975 (Box 21)
    - Nathan M. Pusey- Portrait painting, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Nathan M. Pusey, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Nathan M. Pusey, 1958 (Box 21)
    - Nathan M. Pusey, circa 1959 (Box 21)
    - Nathan M. Pusey, circa 1960 (Box 21)
    - Nathan M. Pusey, 1966 (Box 21)
    - John A. Quelch, circa 1975-circa 1980 (Box 21)
    - Daniel M.G. Raff, circa 1988 (Box 22)
    - Howard Raiffa, circa 1961 (Box 22)
    - Howard Raiffa, circa 1980 (Box 22)
    - Howard Raiffa- Teaching, circa 1985 (Box 22)
    - Howard Raiffa, 1990s (Box 22)
    - Kavasseri V. Ramanathan, circa 1980 (Box 22)
    - U. Srinivasa Rangan, circa 1988 (Box 22)
    - V. Kasturi Rangan, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Gordon C. Rausser, circa 1976 (Box 22)
    - Michael L. Ray, 1971 (Box 22)
    - Thomas C. Raymond, 1970s (Box 22)
    - Thomas C. Raymond- Teaching, circa 1975 (Box 22)
    - Thomas J. Raymond, circa 1956 (Box 22)
    - Jeffrey F. Rayport, circa 1992 (Box 22)
    - Henry Maynard Rees, 1932 (Box 22)
    - C. Richard Reese, circa 1981 (Box 22)
    - Henry B. Reiling, circa 1977 (Box 22)
    - Henry B. Reiling- Teaching, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Henry B. Reiling, circa 1980 (Box 22)
    - John I. Reynolds, circa 1967-circa 1970 (Box 22)
    - James T. Rhea, circa 1973 (Box 22)
    - James T. Rhea, 1980s (Box 22)
    - Eric A.K. Rheman, circa 1976 (Box 22)
    - Stuart U. Rich, circa 1965 (Box 22)
    - Frederick L.W. Richardson, Jr., 1937 (Box 22)
    - Thomas F. Riesing, circa 1975 (Box 22)
    - Edwin Clyde Robbins, 1930s (Box 22)
    - Winnie David Robbins, circa 1957 (Box 22)
    - Michael Roberts, 1990s (Box 22)
    - Paul O. Roberts, circa 1970 (Box 22)
    - Edward J. Robertson, circa 1972 (Box 22)
    - Thomas S. Robertson, circa 1968 (Box 22)
    - Richard D. Robinson, circa 1959 (Box 22)
    - Rita M. Rodriguez, circa 1970 (Box 22)
    - Rita M. Rodriguez, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Rita M. Rodriguez- Teaching, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger, circa 1928-1955 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger, circa 1940 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Teaching, circa 1940 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Teaching, 1946 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger, 1950s (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Photographs by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Photographs by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Photograph by Dick Wolters, circa 1955 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Society of Advancement of Management certificate award, 25 October 1956 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Prediction study award, 1958 (Box 22)
      Fritz J. Roethlisberger, Abraham Zaleznik, and C. Roland Christensen receiving award for The Motivation, Productivity, and Satisfaction of Workers, a Prediction Study.
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger, circa 1960 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger, 1964 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger, circa 1965 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger- Presentation of Counseling in an Organization a Sequel to the Hawthorne Researches, 1967 (Box 22)
    - Fritz J. Roethlisberger, 1966-1967 (Box 22)
    - Vincent J. Roggenveen, circa 1970 (Box 22)
    - David C.D. Rogers, 1960s (Box 22)
    - James Leslie Rollins, 1948 (Box 22)
    - James Leslie Rollins, 1950s (Box 22)
    - James Leslie Rollins, circa 1955 (Box 22)
    - James Leslie Rollins- Photographs by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 22)
    - James Leslie Rollins- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - James Leslie Rollins, circa 1960 (Box 22)
    - James Leslie Rollins, 1971 (Box 22)
    - George B. Roorbach, circa 1930-1933 (Box 22)
    - Richard S. Rosenbloom, circa 1959 (Box 22)
    - Richard S. Rosenbloom, circa 1965 (Box 22)
    - Richard S. Rosenbloom, 1972 (Box 22)
    - Richard S. Rosenbloom- Teaching, 1985 (Box 22)
    - Richard S. Rosenbloom, 1989 (Box 22)
    - John W. Rosenblum, 1970s (Box 22)
    - Eric R. Rosenfeld, circa 1980 (Box 22)
    - Eric R. Rosenfeld, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Donald B. Rosenfield, 1986 (Box 22)
    - William Rotch, circa 1960 (Box 22)
    - Edward Rowley, circa 1965 (Box 22)
    - Richard Stanley Ruback, 1990s (Box 22)
    - Clyde Orval Ruggles, 1942 (Box 22)
    - Clyde Orval Ruggles- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Richard P. Rumelt, circa 1980 (Box 22)
    - John R. Russell, 1970s (Box 22)
    - Walter Rust, 1940s (Box 22)
    - John Ryan, circa 1965 (Box 22)
    - William A. Sahlman, circa 1980-circa 1990 (Box 23)
    - Walter J. Salmon, circa 1960 (Box 23)
    - Walter J. Salmon, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Walter J. Salmon, circa 1990 (Box 23)
    - Malcolm S. Salter, circa 1967 (Box 23)
    - Malcolm S. Salter, circa 1990 (Box 23)
    - Malcolm S. Salter, circa 1990, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Malcolm S. Salter, 1990s (Box 23)
    - Robert Saltonstall, circa 1953 (Box 23)
    - Joseph G. San Miguel, 1970s (Box 23)
    - Edmundo Sanchez-Aguilar, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Thomas H. Sanders, 1935-1949 (Box 23)
    - Thomas H. Sanders- Teaching, 1942 (Box 23)
    - William Sandow, circa 1950 (Box 23)
    - Michael J. Sandretto, 1980s (Box 23)
    - Ratna G. Sarkar, 1996 (Box 23)
    - W. Earl Sasser, 1970s (Box 23)
    - W. Earl Sasser- Teaching, 1975-1978 (Box 23)
    - W. Earl Sasser, circa 1980 (Box 23)
    - W. Earl Sasser, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Roy C. Satchell, circa 1974 (Box 23)
    - Vijay W. Sathe, circa 1990 (Box 23)
    - Charles H. Savage, Jr., circa 1968 (Box 23)
    - I. Richard Savage, circa 1968 (Box 23)
    - Leonard M. Savoie, 1962 (Box 23)
    - Hrand Saxenian, circa 1954 (Box 23)
    - Alberta M. Sbragia, circa 1984 (Box 23)
    - Christian Schaack, circa 1987 (Box 23)
    - Frank K. Schallenberger, circa 1945 (Box 23)
    - David S. Scharfstein, circa 1987 (Box 23)
    - Eileen Schell, circa 1972 (Box 23)
    - Robert O. Schlaifer, circa 1950 (Box 23)
    - Robert O. Schlaifer, circa 1990 (Box 23)
    - Robert O. Schlaifer, 1990 (Box 23)
    - Arthur Schleifer, 1960s (Box 23)
    - Arthur Schleifer, 1970s (Box 23)
    - Leonard A. Schlesinger, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Leonard A. Schlesinger, circa 1989 (Box 23)
    - Leonard A. Schlesinger, 1990s (Box 23)
    - Sumner H. Schlichter, 1940s (Box 23)
    - Sumner H. Schlichter, 1950s (Box 23)
    - Sumner H. Schlichter, 1954 (Box 23)
    - Sumner H. Schlichter- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Sumner H. Schlichter, 1960s (Box 23)
    - Michel M. Schlosser, circa 1974 (Box 23)
    - Richard Schmalansee, circa 1986 (Box 23)
    - Carl Anton Schmalz, 1930s (Box 23)
    - Jurgen Schmandt, circa 1968 (Box 23)
    - Roger W. Schmenner, 1970s (Box 23)
    - Leo Anton Schmidt, 1947 (Box 23)
    - Lewis Schneider, circa 1964-1970 (Box 23)
    - Roy H. Schoeman, circa 1980 (Box 23)
    - Donald R. Schoen, 1948 (Box 23)
    - Lynda A. Schubert, 1980s (Box 23)
    - Samuel S. Schwartz, circa 1950 (Box 23)
    - Bruce R. Scott, circa 1964-1967 (Box 23)
    - Bruce R. Scott, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Bruce R. Scott, 1980s (Box 23)
    - Carol A. Scott, circa 1985 (Box 23)
    - Donald Scott- Photographs by Max Hall, 1930, (Red prints) (Box 23)
    - Donald Scott, 1950 (Box 23)
    - Jerome F. Scott, circa 1950 (Box 23)
    - John T. Sears, circa 1970 (Box 23)
    - John Hunter Sedgwick, circa 1940 (Box 23)
    - Robert M. Segal, circa 1976 (Box 23)
    - John A. Seiler, circa 1956 (Box 23)
    - John A. Seiler, circa 1970 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman, 1940s (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman- With Harry Tosdal, Ross G. Walker, Charles I. Gragg, Harvey Bishop, Frank Gilmore, and Ralph M. Hower, circa 1948 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman- Teaching, 1949 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman, 1950s (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman- Teaching, 1950s (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman, 1955 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman, 1958 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman- 34th AMP Banquet, 1958 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman, circa 1960 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman, circa 1961 (Box 23)
    - Benjamin M. Selekman, 1961 (Box 23)
    - Carlos G. Sequeira, 1993 (Box 23)
    - John K. Shank, circa 1969-1970s (Box 23)
    - Benson Shapiro, 1970s (Box 24)
    - Benson Shapiro- Teaching, 1977 (Box 24)
    - Benson Shapiro- Teaching Executive Education, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Benson Shapiro, circa 1980 (Box 24)
    - Benson Shapiro, 1982 (Box 24)
    - Eli Shapiro, circa 1970 (Box 24)
    - Helen Shapiro, circa 1989 (Box 24)
    - Roy D. Shapiro, circa 1975-1976 (Box 24)
    - Roy D. Shapiro, circa 1985 (Box 24)